#### Contact

liviu.schera@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/liviuschera-521b10289 (LinkedIn) liviuschera.github.io/ (Personal)

#### Top Skills

Reactjs Analytical Skills Reliability

#### Certifications

Front End Development
JavaScript Algorithms and Data
Structures

The Complete Web Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery

Foundational C#

# Liviu Schera

#### Software Developer

Timişoara, Timiş, Romania

# Summary

As a dedicated web developer with six months of experience in digital agencies, I specialize in creating innovative and efficient web solutions. My professional and personal projects reflect a strong commitment to continuous learning and technical excellence.

#### Key Projects:

- Gym Pass: currently working on it. Full stack gym management app build with React, supabase, react query, react router
- Mundus: A ReactJS app that pulls data from three APIs to provide detailed information about all countries, featuring maps and images.
- Image Recognition App: Full-stack app using a Machine Learning API, React, Express, SQL, and PostgreSQL.
- Gym Outlet: Built with React, Firebase, and Stripe for seamless payment integration.
- Client Website and CMS: Designed a responsive site and CMS with SASS, HTML5, MySQL, and PHP.
- Yoga Studio Website: Developed a site that boosted membership by 15%.
- Custom CMS: Created a CMS as part of my Cert IV assessment.
- Noctis Theme for VS Code: Developed a theme with 1million+installs on VS Code Marketplace and 550+ stars on GitHub.

I am passionate about leveraging my skills to contribute to impactful projects and dynamic teams.

Check out my full portfolio and my resume here: https://liviuschera.github.io

# Experience

System Services
IT Technician
August 2022 - April 2023 (9 months)

- Providing break/fix services such as:
- Installing and configuring software and computer systems.
- Troubleshoot and resolve issues with software or hardware.
- Perform repairs on various hardware and equipment on various sites across the state
- installation of servers, switches and routers and standard office equipment
- Computer repair and upgrades for PCs, laptops, printers
- Responsible for keeping tickets updated with accurate time and notes to ensure that both the team and the clients are updated on the progress of their installations/repairs

#### MFDCompany

Web Developer

August 2020 - October 2020 (3 months)

- Worked on a couple of big entrenched projects using a custom build framework based on Vue.JS
- Responsible for keeping work orders updated with notes to ensure that both the team and the clients are updated on the progress of logged tickets

### Digital Agency

Web Developer

May 2020 - July 2020 (3 months)

Brisbane, Queensland, Australia

- Contributed to redesigning itpqld.com built in NuxtJS and Cockpit CMS
- Contributed to building bookkeeping solutions website using VueJS/Nuxt
- Coverted Figma designs to responsive emails with MJML and tested them with Litmus
- Converted Figma UX/UI designs into code

## Education

Charles Darwin University

Certifiacate IV, Computer Technology/Computer Systems

Technology · (January 2017 - December 2017)